原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译:  glida    芝小士和番小茄   斑驳   洗七里
翻译:  冰蓝    熊仔是水饺的老大   预言女巫狼人赛
校对:  平民猎人盗贼赛
时间轴:  三水
后期:  瓜瓜    总监： 怀念浓子的瓜瓜
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
摩  登
家  庭
第八季 第十五集
最新海外影视剧下载
-你好  小卡  -路易丝  你怎么来了
- Hey, Cam. - Louise, what are you doing here?
你不会是不来
You're not dropping out of the
参加今晚的比赛了吧
league championship tonight, are you?
路易丝不来参加比赛了吗
Louise is dropping out of the league championship?
你又开枪打中了自己的腿吗
Did you shoot yourself in the leg again?
天啊  我和我的第一个体育奖杯之间
Oh, my God, we're one win away
只隔着一场胜利的距离
from my first sports trophy,
结果发生了这种破事
and then this happens.
我只说了"你好  小卡"而已
All I said was "Hey, Cam."
今年我邀请了米奇尔
So, this year, I invited Mitchell
参加我的同性恋保龄球队  小甜甜·击倒你队
to join my gay bowling team -- the Britney Spares.
队名是我想的  队服是我设计的
I came up with the team name, I designed the shirts.
-是啊  -谁得到荣誉并不重要
- Yeah. - It's not important who gets the credit.
我们刚开始时  我的保龄球技烂透了
When we first stated, my bowling was, um -- well, it was iffy.
但我一直练习
But then I practiced and I practiced
直到球馆租鞋的人说我"挺像样"
until the shoe-rental guy called me "Decent."
我不是作为队员来的
I'm not here as a teammate.
-而是来办警察公务的  -什么
- I'm here on official police business. - What?
拜托告诉我这不是你
Please tell me that is not you.
那是什么
What is that?
不
Oh, no.
不  不  不
No, no, no.
那是菲茨宝
Hmm. That's Fizbo...
-是啊  -戴着可怕的面具
- Mm-hmm. - ...with a scary mask.
-很明显不是我  -不是他
- That's clearly not me. - It's not him.
不  谁会做这种事啊
No! Who would do that?
谁会把这么美好的东西
Who would take something so beautiful
变得这么丑恶
and turn it into something so ugly?
那人怎么拿到那套小丑服的
How did the guy get the costume?
谁知道
Oh, who knows?
你二爸把它捐给了慈善机构
Your father gave it to charity.
是意外
By accident.
我怎么没听到这场吵架
How did I not hear that fight?
我当时在家吗
Was I in town?
那好吧  结案了
All right, then, uh, case closed.
今晚见
I'll see you guys tonight.
什么  怎么能就此"结案"
What? No "Case closed."
我们还没找到罪犯呢
We haven't even found the perp!
听着  我跟进这个案子的唯一原因
Look, the only reason I was following up on this
就是因为我觉得这可能是你
is 'cause I thought it might be you.
但我们得拿回我的小丑服
Well, yeah, but we have to get my costume back.
帮菲茨宝恢复名誉
We have to restore Fizbo's good name.
但是我们还要去打保龄球的  对吧
Oh, but we're -- we're still gonna go bowling, right?
你捐了我心爱的第二人格
You give away my beloved alter ego,
还不肯给我30秒
and you won't even allow me 30 seconds
让我有情绪反应吗
to have an emotional reaction?
我说那句话时就觉得没过脑子
Yeah. No, it sounded fast as I was saying it.
现在是最后一块
And now for the finishing touch.
给弗兰克的弗兰克牌巧克力塔
Franks for Frank!
我爸的单身派对一定会超赞
Dad's bachelor party's gonna be epic.
你看不出来  所以  击掌
You couldn't see it. That's why -- boom!
鸡肉卷  白葡萄酒  软糕
Chicken wraps, white wine, fudge.
这是单身汉派对
Is this a bachelor party
还是女人坐着看相亲节目《单身汉》的派对
or a party where ladies sit around watching "The Bachelor"?
你为什么给我订XXXL的衣服
And why did you get me a triple-XL?
衣服上写着"我老实跟你说/让我当弗兰克"
导购说洗后会缩水
The lady said it'd shrink in the wash.
-它在垃圾堆里会怎么样  -杰
- How's it gonna do in the trash? - Jay.
开玩笑的  我会用它来当洗车布
Kidding. I'll use it to wash my car.
我爸爸要跟我儿时保姆洛林结婚了
My dad is marrying my old babysitter Lorraine,
而她有个儿子
who has a son,
也就是说我终于要有弟弟了
which means that I am finally getting a brother!
我小时候好想要个弟弟
When I was young, I wanted a brother so much,
我父母给我买了双层床
my folks got me bunk beds.
晚上我会装作我弟弟睡在上层  并跟他聊天
At night, I'd pretend he was up there and talk to him,
他不回答我时  我就想着
and when he didn't answer back, I always just figured,
"马蒂又闹脾气了"
"Well, Marty's in a mood again."
请问这里供应螃蟹[服务坏脾气的人]吗
Excuse me. Do you serve crabs here?
我们为任何人提供服务
We serve anyone.
笑话变老哏是因为它们真的好笑  对吧
Jokes only get old because they're good, right?
说得很好
Nailed it.
菲尔  这是雷
Phil, this is Ray.
看来我们要成为兄弟了
Wow. I guess we're gonna be brothers.
来吧
Bring it in.
不  怎么回事
Oh! No. Oh! What's happening?
我们是兄弟  兄弟不都这样吗
We're brothers! Isn't this what brothers do?
我不知道  但我喜欢
I don't know, but I love it!
这人想摸我的小鸡鸡
This guy totally tried to touch my ding-dong.
我都不知道这是那种派对
I didn't know it was that kind of party.
因为你没看见娘炮的白葡萄酒和软糖吧
I guess you didn't see the white wine and fudge.
白葡萄酒  那可掰不弯我
White wine? That's not gonna get me there.
只有我觉得我今晚
Am I the only one who sees me
会把那家伙掐死吗
choking that guy out tonight?
我不知道
I don't know.
我觉得雷挺不错
I got a good feeling about Ray,
而他对我也挺"激烈"的
and I-I felt a lot of him.
他只是一路坐车过来憋坏了
He's just a little wound up from the drive.
你肯定会发现他是个良好市民的
I'm sure you'll find he's a real solid citizen.
走廊对面的傻瓜没关门
The sap across the hall left his door open.
那是我的房间
That's my room!
看来我得把这瓶药还给你了
Oh. So, I guess you'll need these.
在我们开始前  谢谢大家
Before we start, thanks for agreeing
同意来读我的最新剧本
to do this read through of my latest play,
《深秋满月下的讽刺告别》
"A withering farewell under a harvest moon"...
朗朗
So catch-
冒号  《天使之泪》
...Colon, "The tears of angels."
-朗朗上口  -是吧
- So catchy! - Right?
故事讲的是四个女人为了
It's a story of four women who come together
哀悼逝去的一家之主而相聚
to mourn the loss of the family patriarch.
不  太悲伤了  实在太悲伤了
Oh, no. So sad, so very sad.
慢慢来  疯婆子  我们还没开始呢
Pace yourself, crazy. We haven't even started.
有人去世了  克莱尔
A man died, Claire.
虚构的人
A fake man,
如果他是家族大家长  那就是虚构的老头子
and if he was a patriarch, he was a fake old man,
老头子死了
And old men die.
这个想法
Surely, this is a thought
肯定时不时浮现在你的脑海中  对吧
that has occurred to you from time to time, huh?
请别把我牵扯进来
Please don't make me part of this.
无论如何  读完后
Anyway, when it's over,
尽管分享你们的看法
feel free to share your thoughts --
你们喜欢的  喜爱的部分
what you liked, what you loved,
但也要分享负面看法
but also the negatives --
你们看不懂的部分  不认识的字
What went over your head, any words you didn't know.
我要把最新剧本投稿到青年剧作家文化节
I'm submitting my latest play to a young playwrights festival,
但我想先听人读一遍
but I want to hear it out loud first
以确保所有情感都写到位了
to be sure I've hit all my emotional marks.
或许有人会问  "为什么全是女性角色"
One might ask, "Why all female characters?"
姑且说是懂什么写什么吧
Let's just say, write what you know.
等等  为避免歧义  我是了解女性
Wait. To clarify, I understand women.
不是自我认同为女人
I don't feel like I am one.
110页吗
110 pages?
我们要读到几点才能走啊
What time are we supposed to get out of here?
亲爱的  难不成今晚帅哥有约吗
Oh, honey, you got a hot date tonight?
妈  别这么刻薄  别理她
Mom, don't be mean. Ignore her.
其实我还真交了个男朋友
I actually am in a relationship,
但我一直瞒着所有人
but I've been hiding it from everybody
因为这次我又选了一个
because I have once again chosen somebody
特别不合适的交往对象
that is completely inappropriate.
他叫本  年纪比较大
It's this older guy -- Ben.
他为我妈工作  还和他妈住在一起
He works for my mother, and he lives with his mother.
我总像个扑火的飞蛾
I'm like a moth to a flame
而火指的是不上进
if the flame is an underachieving man-child
屁股上还有卡通人物纹身的妈宝男
with a tasmanian devil tattoo on his butt.
抱歉  这事要拖得比我预想得久
Sorry, this is going to take longer than I expected.
你能在那等我吗
Can you wait there?
没问题
Sure.
反正我妈也把她的牌友闺蜜都叫到家里去了
My mom's got her poker girls over, anyway.
有个叫凯伦的女人总是对我毛手毛脚
This one lady, Karen, she gets real handsy with me.
她也不算没有魅力吧
She's not un-hot, either.
她就像更老更丰满印度版的艾米莉·布朗特
She's like an older, curvy Emily Blunt but Indian.
美国女演员  曾以《穿普拉达的女王》
获得金球奖最佳女配角提名
别妄想能让我吃醋  本
Don't try to make me jealous, Ben.
我在咖啡店的一个常客
One of my regulars at the coffee shop
总问我想不想乘汽艇
is always asking if I want to do some motorboating.
"汽艇"也能指把脸埋在巨乳里并发出汽艇的声音
要不是我会晕船  我就同意了
If I didn't get seasick, I'd go.
我不想把话说得太早
Now, okay, I don't want to get ahead of myself,
但奖杯上有每个队员的名字吗
but does the trophy have each of our names,
还是只有队名
or is it just the team name,
因为我有点想要一个自己的奖杯  但
'cause I kind want one of my own, but --
算了  没事  到时我自己找人刻上去
You know what? No, never mind. I'll just get it engraved.
都到了这种时候
Okay, how can you be thinking
你怎么还能只想着保龄球
about bowling at a time like this?
你是指马上要打保龄球比赛的这种时候吗
You mean as we're going in to our bowling championship?
来短信了
Oh. Text message.
读短信
Read text message.
您有一条来自马丁的短信
You have a message from Martin.
"我脑海总想到你们今晚高举奖杯的画面
"I keep picturing you guys holding the trophy later tonight.
逗你玩
Just kidding.
我不会请你们来我的庆功派对的
You're not invited to my victory party.
哈哈"
Ha ha."
你好  马丁
Hello, Martin.
你好  卡梅隆  你好  米奇尔
Hello, Cameron. Hello, Mitchell.
小甜甜·基佬妮队其余的人呢
Where's the rest of Britney Queers?
是小甜甜·击倒你队  马丁
It's the Britney Spares, Martin.
小甜甜·基佬妮队几周前就被淘汰了
The Britney Queers were eliminated weeks ago.
是的  被我们淘汰的
Yes, by us.
最终  所有人都将成为
Eventually, all will fall
我们基城保龄球手的手下败将
to the Gay City Bowlers.
我记不清了  所有球队名都必须用双关吗
I forget. Do all the names have to be puns?
是的  就像理发店名一样
Yes. It's like hair salons.
一如既往的不幸会  马丁
Unpleasant as always, Martin.
咱们在球馆[小巷]里见
I'll see you in the alley.
这话你对不少男人都说过吧
I'm sure you say that to a lot of men.
米奇尔  是菲茨宝
Mitchell! Fizbo!
-什么  -就在那边
- What? - Over there!
小卡  你觉得有没有可能
Cam-Cam, do you think it's possible
是你太纠结菲茨宝的事
with how upset you are about Fizbo
所以可能出现了幻觉
that-that maybe you're seeing things?
才不是
Oh. No.
也许世上还有另一个紫头发穿60号鞋的人
Maybe it's another guy with purple hair and a size 23 shoe.
或许丹尼斯·罗德曼也在这打保龄球呢
Maybe Dennis Rodman bowls here!
NBA知名退役球星
咱们开始啦
And we begin.
詹姆斯·皮克特客厅里的灯亮着
Lights up on the living room of James Pickett.
家具和陈设告诉我们他是个有钱人
The furnishings and art tell us he was a wealthy man,
但钱买不来品味
but his money couldn't buy taste.
四个穿着黑色衣服的女人走了进来
Enter four women in black
她们刚从葬礼上回来
returning from a funeral.
首先  詹姆斯的遗孀克洛伊·杜布瓦皮克特
First, James' widow Chloe Dubois-Pickett...
是我
That's me!
一位美丽的已婚法国女士
...A beautiful french commoner who married up.
乌啦啦
Ooh, la la.
然后是贝莉  他的外孙女
Next is Bailey, the granddaughter --
可爱又聪明
cute as a button and just as smart.
我喜欢她
I like her.
接着是詹姆斯的妹妹
Following her is James' sister,
阿尔玛·迪勒教授  60多岁
Professor Alma Diller, 60s.
世上没有她解不了的难题
There's no problem she can't solve
除了自己的孤单寂寞
except her own loneliness.
最后是詹姆斯的女儿  凯特
Finally, James' daughter Kate --
迷人  认真  毒舌
attractive, intense, sharp-tongued,
热情转瞬即逝
fleeting moments of warmth.
Fleeting moments of warmth?
我明白了
I get it.
这就是在讲我们四个人
This is the story of the four of us
不过套上了一层曼尼改编版滤镜
through some sort of distorted Manny lens.
就因为我聪明  我就得是老处女吗
Yeah, just because I'm smart, I end up a spinster?
你知道如果我会不晕船的话
You know what I could be doing right now
现在会在干嘛吗
if I didn't get seasick?
冷静冷静
Okay, calm down.
这些角色结合了
These characters are a compilation
我所认识的好多其他女性  不是你们
of many other women I've known, not you people.
好了  开始吧
Okay, let's start.
凯特一进来就直接到了书橱面前
Kate enters and crosses straight to the credenza,
迫不及待地给自己倒了一杯红酒
as she pours herself a much-needed glass of wine...
好吧
Mm. Right.
说实话  我真不敢相信
To be honest, I can't believe
这老麻烦拖到现在才死
the old grump didn't die years ago.
漂亮
Nice.
我的第一句词就是说我死去父亲的坏话
My first line is something horrible about my dead dad.
你觉得我是有多冷漠啊
How cold do you think I am?
我刚不是说了  不是你吗
Didn't I just say it's not you?
难道不是吗
Isn't it, though?
什么
What?
老人去世不算事儿
Old people die, get over it?
那不是你20分钟前说的吗
That was, like, 20 minutes ago.
等下
Okay, now, hang on a second.
感觉你们还得吵一会儿
Okay, this seems like a whole thing,
我去喝个水  很快
so I'm just gonna go grab a water real quick.
不是吧
Oh, come on.
你在和谁发短信
Who are you texting?
没谁
Ahh! No one.
-我只是在看我的星座运程  -骗人
- I'm just reading my horoscope. - Liar.
哪会有人这么晚看自己的星座运程
Why would anyone read their horoscope so late in the day?
事情都已经发生完了
Everything's already happened.
有个男孩  是不是
There's a dude, isn't there?
什么  不是
What? No.
拿着手机鬼鬼祟祟
Sneaking off with your phone,
洗了头
the clean hair,
穿着唯一合身的一件胸罩  从实招来
your one bra that fits properly -- spill.
好吧
Okay, fine.
是有个男孩
There is a dude.
天呐  别又是个高中生
Oh, god, it's not another high-school boy, is it?
不  他成年了
No. He's legal.
只是在其他方面让人有点尴尬
He's just embarrassing in a different way.
你知道吗  你从小到大一直这样
You know you've been like this your whole life --
对浪漫与情欲方面的自己感到羞耻
ashamed of the romantic, sexual part of you.
说实话  感觉像你觉得自己不配有爱情一样
Honestly, it seems like you think you don't deserve it,
但你配啊
but you do.
如果这个男生有趣  对你也不错
And if this guy is fun and good to you
不骑摩托  就别为难自己了
and doesn't ride a scooter, let it be okay.
海莉
Haley.
谢谢
Thanks.
姑娘们  我不知道
Ladies, I don't know
这现在在上演什么感情大戏
what emotional thing is playing out right now,
但保留一下情感  用在戏剧上如何
but how about you save it for over there?
我发给你了一个超可爱的视频
And then I sent you the cutest video
母狮子在哺乳一只小狗
of a puppy nursing on a mama lion,
你回了什么
and what do you text back?
她把他养胖
She's getting him fat
这样把它当午饭吃掉时更美味
so that he tastes better at lunch?
那又怎样  我这人搞笑也是罪吗
Yeah, so what? My crime is I'm hilarious?
我们能回到剧本上吗
Can we get back to this, please?
凯特刚说她不敢相信
Kate just said she couldn't believe
她爸没早点死  然后
her father didn't die sooner, then --
遗孀杜布瓦倒卧在椅子上  伤心
The widow Dubois slumps in a chair, emotional.
亲爱的[法语]
Ohh, ma cherie,
你爸爸听到你说这么麻木不仁的话
your papa would be devastated to hear you say
会伤心死的
such insensitive things.
不是吧
Really?
你确定要搞口音这套吗
Are you gonna do the whole accent thing?
瞧瞧  我们看到了什么
Lo and behold -- what do we see?
黑桃Q不见了  它会在哪呢
The queen of spades is gone! Where could she be?
在弗兰克口袋里  我看到你放进去了
In Frank's pocket. I saw you put it there.
真的啊
So it is!
魔术真棒  菲尔
Great trick, Phil.
你真是"好"托儿  雷
And nice assist, Ray.
这不该是单身汉派对吗
I thought this was supposed to be a bachelor party.
有女性的娱乐项目哪去了
Where's the female entertainment?
这个你不用担心
Oh, don't you worry about that.
Mr.Sandman - The Chordettes
* 睡魔先生  给我个梦中情人 *
* Mr. Sandman, bring me a dream *
* 要让他是我见过最帅的人 *
* Make him the cutest that I've ever seen *
* 赐他两瓣玫瑰与三叶草般的嘴唇 *
* Give him two lips like roses and clover *
* 告诉他那些寂寞的夜晚... *
* Then tell him that his lonesome nights... *
你在做什么
What are you doing?!
宣布死亡时间
Calling time of death.
不是你们  女士们
Oh, not you ladies.
你们当然还活力充沛
You're still very vital, of course.
我们真的很感谢
Hey, we really appreciate
你们在战时为国家做的贡献
all the riveting you did during the war.
老爸正享受呢
Dad was enjoying them.
走了也行
Just as well.
我就要结婚了
I'm about to be married.
我没必要被那些臀臀臀[棒棒棒]诱惑
I don't need to be tempted by all those bum, bum, bums.
你准备的活动就这些了吗
Oh, is that it for the planned activities?
不  好戏才刚开始
No, we're just getting started.
接下来一小时玩赌注五美元的乌诺牌
For the next hour, it's a $5 buy-in game of Uno,
然后下楼去老船长餐厅
then downstairs to Captain Scupper's,
吃沙漠中最好的牡蛎
the best oysters in the desert.
最后  先生们  打上领带
And finally, put on your neckties, gentlemen,
因为我有四张楼座票去看尼尔...
'cause I have four balcony seats to Mr. Neil...
拜托是戴蒙德[歌手]
Please say "Diamond."
萨达卡[歌手]
...Sedaka.
多么丰富的夜晚
What a night!
我们冰不够了
Oh, we need some ice.
我去去就回
I'll be right back.
乌诺牌是什么
What the hell's Uno?
有点像用脑版的"疯狂八点"游戏
Sort of a thinking man's Crazy Eights.
与其在这里玩桌游牌
Instead of playing cards up here,
楼下有家赌场  还有我们大人该喝的烈酒
there is a casino downstairs with actual big-boy drinks.
我跟他去
I'm right behind him.
我们路上叫上菲尔
We'll grab Phil on the way.
或者让他找我们  他应该觉得更有趣吧
Or wouldn't it be fun for him to try and find us?
他肯定会喜欢的
Oh, he'll love that!
路易丝  我刚看到那个变态的冒名小丑
Hey, Louise, I just saw that psycho imposter clown
在外面垃圾箱旁恐怖地瞪着我
out by the dumpster giving me threatening looks.
-听着  肥子宝...  -是菲茨宝
- Look, Flouncy... - It's Fizbo.
我说的是你
I'm talking to you.
我没时间听你废话什么小丑
I don't have time for your clown nonsense.
我们要赢下冠军
We've got a championship to win.
我去跟球瓶[靛蓝]女孩队一起暖身了
I'm gonna go warm up with the pindigo girls.
为什么这非要在今天发生呢
Why does this have to be happening today?
米奇尔  或许就因为是今天才发生的
Mitchell, maybe it's happening because it's today.
或许有人想扰乱我思绪
Maybe somebody is trying to get in my head
让我不能好好比赛
to throw me off my game.
亲爱的  你真以为有人会在意到...
Oh, honey, do you really think people care enough to --
光现在就能看到有六个人
Hey, you know what, there are six people just in my eyesight
会不惜一切破坏我的连胜
that would do anything to break my winning streak.
比如  马丁
For instance, Martin.
他从没原谅我
He's never forgiven me
让他误以为你爸爱他那事
for making him feel like your father was in love with him.
不可能是马丁
Okay, it couldn't have been Martin.
我们看到他之后刚过三秒
We saw him, like, three seconds
你就以为你见到菲茨...
before you thought that you saw Fiz--
-是真的看到  -好吧
- Actually saw. - Okay.
他跟我爸是怎么回事来着
And what's this about my dad?
行行  不是马丁
Fine. It's not Martin.
但绝对有可能是卡普兰先生
But it certainly could be Senor Kaplan.
一  二  三  四  五  六[西语]
Uno, dos, tres, cuatro, cinco, seis.
你好  卡普兰先生
Hola, Senor Kaplan.
你要是来呛声  我没兴趣听
If you're here to talk trash, I'm not interested.
你20分钟前在哪里
Where were you 20 minutes ago,
有谁能证明你的行踪吗
and can anybody account for your whereabouts?
虽然不关你事
Not that it's any of your business,
但我刚去照相亭拍单人照去了
but I happened to be in the photo booth taking some solos.
我新护照照片要用第三张
I'm gonna use number three for my new passport.
要我就用第二张  眼里闪烁着光芒
I would use number two. There's a twinkle in your eye.
但我认为你20分钟前
But I have a different theory
是在别的地方
as to where you were 20 minutes ago,
而且你会有刚好足够的时间
and it would have given you exactly enough time
换下小丑服  穿上保龄球服...
to change out of a clown costume into your bowling outf--
-怎么了  -不不不
- What's wrong? Wha... - No. No, no.
我刚看到  看到菲  菲茨宝
I just saw -- I just saw Fi-- Fizbo
出现在  在镜子里
in -- in -- in the mirror.
我不知道你是怎么回事  塔克
I don't know what's going on with you, Tucker,
但用我的家乡话来说就是"脑子疯了"[西语]
but in my culture, we like to call it loco en la cabeza.
行了  别装了  你是加拿大人
Okay, you know what? Knock it off. You're Canadian.
"你们似乎都忘了我并不孤独  我有艾伯特
"You all seem to forget I'm not alone. I have Albert.
我敢打赌你搜遍全世界
You can search the world,
也找不到另一更忠诚  更深情的...
and I defy you to find a more devoted, loving...
鹦鹉"
Parrot."
"我以前很喜欢跟阿尔伯特聊天
"I used to like talking to Albert,
可后来我们因为一块饼干吵了架"
but then we got into a fight over a cracker."
"两人看着这个寡妇伤心地敲击琴键时
"Kate whispers to Bailey as they watch the widow
凯特对贝莉说"
sadly plunking notes on the piano."
"咱们还得陪她多久
"How long do we have to stay with her?
我们可以走了吧"
We can leave now, right?"
"我早知道要是你爸死了
"I knew when your papa died,
你就绝对不会再来看我了"
I would never see you again."
"不论我做了什么
"No matter what I do,
你就是拒绝接受我已接受了你"
you refuse to accept that I accepted you."
"没这回事
"Mais non.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我今天心情太百感交集了"
I'm just so emotional today."
"你心情复杂是应该的  克洛伊
"But of course you are, Chloe.
很抱歉我让你觉得自己是个外人"
And I'm sorry if I made you feel like an outsider."
"我爱你  你知道吗  我爱你"
"I love you, you know? Je t'aime."
"我也爱你"
"I love you, too."
灯光灭
Black out.
太棒了  太棒了
Bravo! Bravo!
你不是吧  曼尼
Really, Manny?
我的角色为了一块饼干跟鹦鹉吵了一架
My character gets into a fight with a parrot over a cracker?
我把这故事当秘密告诉你的
I told you that story in confidence.
姐告诉你
And for the record...
我一点也不像我的角色
I am nothing like my character.
姐一点也不孤独
I'm not lonely at all.
追我的人排队排老长了
I have tons of options.
我现在就要去见一个
I'm actually going to see one right now.
多亏了海莉
And thanks to Haley,
我再也不会羞于谈他了
I'm no longer ashamed of talking about him.
是谁啊
Ooh! Who is it?
-没谁  -叫什么名字
- No one. - What's his name?
没什么
Nothing.
好吧  如果没有其他反馈的话...
Well, if that's it for the feedback...
-我还有  其实  -好吧
- No, actually... - Oh. Yay.
我觉得结尾有点老套
For me, the ending felt a little trite.
有很多好的部分
There's a lot of good stuff in there,
但是那一大堆"对不起  对不起
but the whole "I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
我爱你  我爱你"的  我只是
I love you, I love you" -- I just --
觉得女人心思比那更复杂一些
I think women are more complicated than that.
别听她胡说  曼尼
Don't listen to her, Manny.
结尾很好
The ending was beautiful.
只是有些女人不善于
It's just that some women have a hard time
表达自己的感情
expressing their feelings.
又来了
Oh, this again?
歌洛莉亚  我可是很善于表达的人
Gloria, I'm a very feeling person.
是吗
Oh, really?
你在给我的生日贺卡上就写
From the woman that writes in my birthday cards
"祝好  克莱尔"
"Best, Claire."
这怎么不暖心了
How is that not warm?
我可是在给你最"好"的祝福
I am wishing you quite literally the best.
我是你家人
I am a person in your family.
不是给你修眉毛的
I am not the woman that does your eyebrows.
我为什么会给修眉毛的送生日贺卡
Why would I send her a birthday card?
问题是  你为什么不写"爱你的克莱尔"
The question is why can't you write "Love, Claire"?
我都会写"爱你的歌洛莉亚"
I write "Love, Gloria."
还在"我"上点了一大颗心
I even dot the "I" with a huge heart.
我对你说我爱你  你回我"我也是"
I tell you that I love you, and you say "Me, too."
为什么  你为什么就是不能说你爱我
Why? Why can't you tell me that you love me?
我也不知道为什么我说不出口
I don't know why I can't tell you that I --
我有段时间愿意说的
There was a time when I wanted to,
但错过了那时刻  再加上时光流逝
and then the moment passed and time went by
再说就感觉很刻意
and then it just felt forced.
你整天说这句话
You -- you say it all the time.
某些人会觉得反而稀释了话中感情呢
One could argue that dilutes it.
所以是我的错
Oh, so now it's my fault?
我这么跟你吵
I am lashing out at you
是因为我已经不止一次
because this is not the first time
被人这么指责了
I've been accused of this.
很抱歉我之前一直都没说过  歌洛莉亚
I am sorry I haven't said it before, Gloria.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
好了
Okay.
我的天  你说得对  的确很老套
My God, you're right. It is trite.
-你可以的  萨姆  -加油
- You got this, Sam! - Come on.
加油
Come on!
而你  要是再扔一个洗沟球
You on the other hand -- you throw one more gutter ball,
我就会诬陷你杀了人
And I will literally frame you for murder.
别有压力
No pressure.
那是怎么回事
I wonder what that's about.
你俩看上去很亲密嘛
You two seem awfully chummy.
如果你说的"亲密"指的是
Well, if by "chummy," you mean,
"处于一段来电的激情恋爱关系"
"In the throes of an electric sexual relationship,"
对  我们以你的保龄球发誓我们亲密得很
then, yes, you bet your bowling balls we're chummy.
我的天
Oh, my gosh.
这就说得通了
I just put it all together.
你俩都是菲茨宝
You're both Fizbo.
我跟你们其中一个在一起
When I'm with one of you,
另一个就去穿小丑服  制造完美不在场证明
The other's wearing the costume, creating the perfect alibi.
灵光一闪啊
Light-bulb moment!
又在说小丑的事了
This clown thing again.
塔克你听我说  如果我想报复你
Look, Tucker, if I wanted to get back at you
报复一些比如像是
for, oh, I don't know, say something like
撮合我跟你直男岳父之类的事
setting me up with your straight father-in-law,
我绝对不会用
I certainly wouldn't do it
-偷走你傻逼宝服的手段  -是菲茨宝
- by stealing your stupid bozo suit. - It's Fizbo.
亲爱的  你人品最高尚了
Way to take the high road, sweetie.
首先  我会侵入你电邮
First, I'd hack your e-mails,
然后我会创几个社交网站小号
then I'd create several fake social-media accounts,
用来散播全方位抹黑  泼你脏水的谣言
which I would use to mount the multi-pronged smear campaign
让你与所有你爱的人的关系四分五裂
to drive a wedge between you and everything you love.
这话或许有点吓到人啊
That's maybe a bit of a red flag.
接着我会用你名义办几张信用卡
And then I'd get several credit cards in your name
并着手进行一场大规模身份盗窃计划
and then embark on a massive identity-theft scheme
把你搞到破产
that would leave you bankrupt
如果老天开眼  甚至还让你被刑事起诉
and, with any luck at all, facing criminal charges.
这才是我的报复方式
That's what I'd do.
好啦  她就是个小调皮蛋
Okay. She's a bit of a handful, huh?
我刚在想  或许我们这周末
You know, I was thinking, maybe we should take a beat
去见你父母的事可以再缓缓
on meeting your parents this weekend.
你怎么看  好啦
What do you say? All right.
什么
What?
高  太高招了
Bravo! Bravo.
如果你觉得你这段浮夸的报仇独白
If you think your little over-the-top revenge monologue
能够令我转移怀疑对象
is gonna throw me off your scent,
那你就大错特错了
then you are sorely mistaken.
打开你的包
Now open your bag.
什么
What?
你们所有人  打开你们的包
All of you, open your bags!
你们不用...  小卡  你快停下
You don't have... Cam, you got to stop.
快打开
Open them!
你有妄想症  你在发神经
You're paranoid. You are paranoid.
没有人穿着你...
No one is dressing up...
靠  最恨你对我错的时候了
Oh, damn it, I hate it when you're right.
什么  他在那里
What -- Oh! There he is!
追  快把他拿下
Chase him! Get him!
站住  你个冒牌货
Stop! Imposter!
请关上门  女士  我们在追犯人
Close your door, ma'am! We're in pursuit!
-好啦  悠点  悠点  -谢谢
- Okay, okay, okay. - Thank you!
好啦
Okay.
我们追丢他了
We lost him.
等等  他落了面具
Wait. His mask.
闻起来有啤酒跟起司薯条味
It smells like beer and cheese fires.
-米奇尔  简直神探啊  -太好啦
- Oh, Mitchell, that's good investigative work. - Yes.
你把犯人缩小到
You've narrowed it down
保龄球馆里的所有人啦
to everyone in the bowling alley.
我只剩一张牌啦
Uno.
你在这里啊
There you are.
我们到处找你呢
We've been looking all over for you.
你们有来这里找过吗  派对举办处这里
Did you check in here, in the room where the party is?
别担心  我们没忘掉你
Don't worry. We didn't forget about you.
希望你们做的事
I hope it was worth it.
比我们错过的老船长餐厅更值得一去
We missed our reservation to Captain Scupper's.
别担心  菲尔  我们吃过了
Don't worry, Phil. We ate.
赌场经理送了免费鲜虾鸡尾酒
Pit boss sent some shrimp cocktails
到我们的双骰赌桌
over to our craps table.
还有一些普通的真鸡尾酒  对吧
Along with some regular cocktails, am I right?
对啊
Yeah!
你  你得在场才知道笑点
You -- you had to be there.
我懂  你们吃了虾喝了酒
I get it. You had shrimp and drinks.
如果不会给你们造成麻烦
Now, if it's not too much trouble,
我们能继续走安排的行程了吗
maybe we could get back on schedule.
我们可不能错过萨达卡的暖场表演
We don't want to miss Sedaka's opening act --
矮人版小理查
Extremely little richard.
小理查是出生于1932年的老牌男歌手
天啊  他可真是超矮
Good golly, is he small!
计划改变了  我把那些票
Change of plans -- I traded those tickets
换成了"亚瑟王的逼中剑"的票
for seats to "Sexcalibur."
-你干嘛了  -是色情版的"中世纪秀"
- You what? - It's a dirty "Medieval times."
你不是吧
Are you kidding me?
没关系的  菲尔
It's okay, Phil.
我等了79年看尼尔·萨达卡的表演
I waited 79 years to see Neil Sedaka.
我不介意再等79年
I can wait another 79.
不行  老爸  你又烂好人了
No, dad. You're being too nice.
这是你的单身汉派对  不是你的
This is your bachelor party, not yours!
今晚都让你给毁了
You're ruining this whole night.
你在计划的时候就毁了今晚
You ruined it when you planed it.
把你的脏手指给我拿开
And get that finger out of my face.
没有人可以抢走我爸的派对
Nobody hijacks my dad's party,
也没有人能控制我的手指放哪
and nobody tells me where to put my finger.
熊孩子来啦
Here we go.
我十岁的时候想要个弟弟
I wanted a brother when I was 10,
不是想要只有十岁的弟弟
not a 10-year-old brother!
你才是幼稚鬼
You're the baby!
你虽然比我大  可你才是幼稚的那个
You're older, but you're the baby.
你才比不上马蒂
You're no Marty!
虽然算不上打架  但还是需要拦一下吧
It's not much of a fight, but maybe we should --
我知道  我原以为会越打越精彩
I know. I thought it was gonna get good.
行了  住手  不许打了
All right, that's enough. Stop.
菲尔  你这种表现太荒谬了
Phil, you're being ridiculous.
雷  我不认识你  但你看起来就是一个蠢货
Ray, I don't know you, but you seem like a horse's ass.
住手 可以了 成熟一点
All right, now! Grow up!
稍微有点大人样儿
Start acting like gentlemen.
不知你们两个介不介意
Uh, would you two mind
先一步去走廊等一会
stepping out in the hall for a second?
我有几句话想跟菲尔谈一谈
I need to have a word with Phil.
行吧  但你尽量快一点
All right, but hurry up.
我们可不能错过第一个少妇开始脱衣
We don't want to miss the unlacing of the first wench.
你知道吧  我真的很感激
You know, I really appreciate
你为了我的单身派对准备的这一切
all you've done arranging my party,
但其实做什么活动我都会很高兴
But, you know, I'm happy doing whatever.
是不是有什么别的事让你不开心了
Is something else bothering you?
我也不清楚
I don't know.
只是太多事情在改变  爸
So much is changing, dad.
我可能是有点害怕这将会是一个时代的终结
I guess I'm kind of afraid that this is the end of an era.
现在我得适应要和洛林与那家伙分享你
Now I have to share you with Lorraine, with that.
你不会失去我的
You're not losing me.
而且事实上  你以后会更经常见到我了呢
As a matter of fact, you're gonna be seeing a lot more of me.
洛林和我其实也在商量这个想法
Lorraine and I have been kind of kicking around the idea
就是搬到加州来
of moving to California.
为了离我更近吗
To be closer to me?
是啊
Yes.
也为了离雷稍微远一点
And to be farther from Ray.
路易丝  我们刚刚又看到恶魔版菲茨宝了
Hey, Louise, we just saw evil Fizbo again.
是真的  我刚才亲眼看见
It's true. I was there.
但我们追到停车场就追丢了
We lost him in the parking lot.
是啊  我们检查了每一辆车
Yeah, we looked in every car.
天啊  路易丝  你肯定能做点什么的吧
Geez, Louise, there has to be something you can do.
好的  明早我立刻去查
Fine. First thing tomorrow, I'll look into it
但前提你专心打这场保龄球赛
if you can focus on bowling.
-我可以  -你在这里啊
- I can. - There you are.
我刚才到处找你  轮到你上场了
I've been looking all over for you. It's your turn.
对不起  我刚才去了厕所
Sorry. I was in the ladies room.
给我的小屁屁贴镇痛药布
I was putting icyhot on my hammies.
你手怎么了吗
D-did you do something to your hand?
我刚才玩空气曲棍球的时候弄伤了
I just hurt it playing air hockey.
他们几个月前就把空气曲棍球桌撤掉了
They got rid of the air hockey table months ago.
不是啦  我是指...
Uh -- nothing. I mean, I was --
等等  等一下  慢着听我说
Wait -- w-wait -- wait a minute.
你刚刚消失了
You go missing,
然后你说不清原由地伤到了你的手  而且
Then you mysteriously hurt your hand, and t--
好的很好  这个面具里留下的口红印
Okay, okay -- there is lipstick in this mask,
它  它和你啤酒杯上的口红印同色
and it is -- it is the same shade as the lipstick on your beer.
你居然是假菲茨宝吗
You're Fizbo?
你居然涂口红啊
You wear lipstick?
但你是跟我们一队的啊
But you're on our team.
你为什么要这样做啊
Why would you do this?
因为我快被你恶心死了
Because you bug me.
就因为这样吗
That's it?
队伍名也是你选  队伍服也是你设计
You picked the team name, you designed the shirts,
所有的荣誉都让你揽了
You take all the credit.
所有的事都是以你为中心
Everything's about you.
你扰乱他的思维  好让他害我们队输掉比赛
You messed with his head so he'd lose us the team championship.
然后自己当上队长之路就一片光明
Yeah, opening the door for -- for you to be captain.
本来就应该是我当队长
I should be captain.
把我的菲茨宝还给我
Give me my Fizbo.
然后你从我的面前消失
You get out of my face.
等一下  稍等我确认一下
Wait, wait, no. Hold on. Hold on.
我们还有任何希望赢这场比赛吗
Is there still a chance that we could win this?
除非我们能一球击倒57个球瓶
Not unless we can pick up 57 pins in one frame.
好的  你现在从他面前消失
Yeah. And you get out of his face.
-你好  您父亲胯下的作品  -叫"米奇尔"就行了
- Hello, fruit of your father's loins. "Mitchell"'s fine.
既然聊到了杰
You know, speaking of jay --
是你自己提起的
You brought him up.
好吧  你爸爸和我  曾来电过一会儿
Well, your father and I had a moment...
就在几年之前
Uh-huh. ...A couple of years ago
第6季第20集
在他假装是基佬
when he was pretending to be gay
来参加我们的保龄球赛时那会儿
so that he could bowl in our league.
我知道他说了那全是演的
I know he said it was all an act,
但我从他身上所感受到的
but what I felt from him --
感觉实在太真实了
it was just so very real.
好了马丁  我也不想泼你冷水
Okay, Martin, I hate to break this to you,
但我的父亲很有可能是
but my dad is potentially
这个星球上最直的男人
the straightest man on the planet.
我知道  但尽管如此
Yeah, but notwithstanding,
你能不能考虑把他的电话号码留给我
do you think maybe you could give me his phone number?
和他之间我总感觉有故事还没有完结
It's just always felt like unfinished business to me.
我绝不会把他的电话号码给你的
I am not giving you his phone number.
我愿意给你我的奖杯
I'll give you my trophy.
你记一下是 310...
It's 310...